talentnow.com 2011-12-22

# talentnow: Privacy Policy

Talentnow has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to protect your personal information and educating you on how we use it. This policy applies to activities in which you engage, and data collected, on Talentnow ("Talentnow" or "Talentnow.com") or through email campaigns performed on our customers’ behalf (collectively, the "Site") but does not apply to any other Website or offline point of contact between Talentnow, or any other company, and consumers. Please review this policy periodically as we may modify it from time to time. Each time you visit Talentnow or provide us with information, by doing so you are accepting the practices described in this policy at that time.

Information Collected

Your Personally Identifiable Information Collected by Talentnow:

During our user sign up process we collect certain information such as your name, email, address etc. This information can be personally identifiable. You may always choose not to provide such Personally Identifiable Information; however, this may limit our ability to provide you with certain functionality on Talentnow.

We may also collect demographic and other data, which may include Personally Identifiable Information. This information is provided by you, and you may always choose not to provide information about yourself.

Profile

If you create your profile on Talentnow, you will be required to provide us with personally identifiable information. You will also enter other professional information such as your skill, experience, education which will allow others to search for professionals like you. On Talentnow, by default, your profile will be public and registered users of Talentnow will be able to search your profile. We reserve the right to use your profile in whole or in parts in media, publications online or offline.

Talentnow also provides functionality for you to hide your contact information such as Name, Email and Phone.

Personally Identifiable Information Collected by Talentnow's Business Partners

Talentnow works with employers, third-party advertising companies, sponsors and other companies with whom we do business ("Business Partners") to place advertising on our site and in email communications sent to our registered users and to recipients of job opportunities, search alerts, and other communications related to the Talentnow Service. Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad, may be used to serve advertising to you.

\- Talentnow may correlate or match registered user information, including Personally Identifiable Information, with information held by our Business Partners to target ads or otherwise improve the effectiveness of our service. Our Business Partners may read or set cookies on your hard drive, use pixel tags, track which ads you have viewed, or collect other information about you.

\- From time to time, Talentnow may also have special offers that are sponsored by a Business Partner. In order to participate in these offers, you may be required to follow a separate registration process. If you consent to receive information from a Business Partner, through an opt-out process, Talentnow may pass your information to such Business Partners.

\- Talentnow may also offer goods or services for purchase available by our Business Partners. If you purchase goods or services offered through Talentnow by a Business Partner, then you may be required to submit Personally Identifiable Information in order to complete the transaction and Talentnow may provide your Personally Identifiable Information to such Business Partner for that purpose.

\- In some cases, we may enter into a promotional relationship with a Business Partner in which we prominently display their brand name or trademarks on pages that appear the same as or very similar to the pages of the Talentnow service. These pages are known as "Co-Branded Pages" and these particular Business Partners are known as "Co-Branded Business Partners."

\- If the page on which you submit information is a Co-Branded Page, or was accessed by clicking on a link on a Co-Branded Page, then we may share your personal information with the associated Co-Branded Business Partner. Co-Branded Business Partners may use your personal information in accordance with their own privacy policies. Talentnow disclaims all liability for the privacy policies and procedures on any Business Partner or Co-Branded Business Partner Web site.

\- You will need to contact the Co-Branded Business Partner to instruct them directly regarding your preferences for the use of your personal information by them. Additionally, you agree that Talentnow may use and disclose all such information so submitted to such Co-Branded Business Partners in the same manner in which we are entitled to use and disclose any other information you submit to us (see Use of Personally Identifiable Information by Business Partners below).

Cookies : Talentnow wants to optimize your experience by ensuring that the most relevant information, searches and offers are displayed to you while using the Talentnow web site. A common manner in which to do this is by placing cookies on your computer. Cookies are strings of text and numbers that can identify your computer to us when you visit our site, and which may be correlated with your Personally Identifiable Information in our log files.

IPAddress: We log standard information such as your IP address along with the URL from which you came to our site and the URLs visited on our site, which may or may not contain some Personally Identifiable Information. When we send messages to you or others, we may provide a URL link to the Talentnow site that contains an alphanumeric identifier, which allows us to identify the person to whom we sent the message so that we can personalize our content for that individual.

PixelTags: Talentnow uses pixel tags to gather information about the emails we send to our registered users and to recipients of messages. Pixel tags are tiny graphic files, not visible to the human eye, that are included in our HTML-encoded email messages. When such a message is opened in an HTML-capable email program, the recipient's computer will access our server to retrieve the pixel tag file, allowing us to record and store, along with your email address, the date and time the recipient viewed the invite or reminder, that the recipient's email program is capable of receiving HTML-encoded email, and other standard logging information. The pixel tag also may see or read cookies. For more information about cookies and how to disable their use, see the section below on "Use of Cookies."

Use of Information

Use of Personally Identifiable Information by Talentnow:

\- We use the collected Personally Identifiable Information to verify you and to contact you in connection with your transactions, postings and other activities on the site, to forward to you messages from other Users, to communicate with you about Job opportunities of interest to you and to operate the Talentnow service.

\- These types of communications may contain commercial messages, such as banner ads and special offers. Each communication we send to you, other than communications sent to you for the sole purpose of addressing a technical or operational issue regarding the Talentnow service, will give you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving further such communications from us.

\- Use of our invitation service to tell a friend about our site or a job opportunity, or to participate in a referral chain, requires that you enter your friend’s email address. We will automatically send your friend email inviting him or her to visit the site or view the opportunity. Talentnow stores this information to send this email, to register a friend connection if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of the Talentnow referral program. Your friend may contact us at Talentnow to request that we remove this information from view in our active database (Please use Talentnow Privacy in the subject line).

\- Talentnow uses your Personally Identifiable Information to help us provide you with personalized content, advertising, and commercial messages (collectively, "Content").

\- Talentnow does not sell, share or otherwise provide any "Personally Identifiable Information" you give to us with any Business Partner without your consent, which may be obtained through an opt-in request (see Use of Personally Identifiable Information by Business Partners below), unless required by law, court order or as required to technically operate the service, or to complete a transaction or order.

\- Talentnow does reserve the right to share your Personally Identifiable Information with its parent, subsidiary or affiliated entities ("affiliated entities" are those companies owned or controlled by Talentnow's parent company).

Use of Personally Identifiable Information by Other Users:

Other users will be able to view the information that you provide on your Profile.Other users may choose to contact you. Similarly, you may contact other users on the site.

* Use of our invitation service to tell a friend about our site or a job opportunity, or participation in a referral chain, requires that you enter your friend’s email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site or view the opportunity. Talentnow stores this information to send this one-time email, to register a friend connection if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of the Talentnow referral program. Your friend may contact us at Talentnow to request that we remove this information from view in our active database (Please use Talentnow Privacy in the subject line).

Use of Your Personally Identifiable Information by Talentnow's Business Partners:

Contracted employers using Talentnow to send their jobs to you may receive your contact information (name and email address) from another user on Talentnow, from one of their employees participating in a Talentnow referral campaign, or by using other means outside the context of Talentnow, such as their own database of resumes or a third party database. In all cases, the employer using Talentnow to contact you is subject to this Privacy Commitment. And, you may at any time choose to opt out of receiving further communication from Talentnow. However, even if Talentnow blocks further use of your contact information, Talentnow cannot prevent employers who have obtained your name and email address independently from Talentnow from contacting you directly. Talentnow recommends contacting the employer directly if you wish to opt-out of further communication. * In order to provide other offers of particular interest to you, Talentnow may share demographic, geographic, and other Personally Identifiable Information with its Business Partners with your explicit consent (opt-in).

PLEASE NOTE: The privacy practices of advertisers and other companies who provide services or advertising through our site are not covered by this privacy commitment. Please contact those companies directly for more information about their privacy practices. If you wish to prevent those companies from setting cookies on your browser, you may set your browser to refuse cookies or to warn you before setting a cookie. Disabling cookies set by companies whose products or services are advertised on this site may affect your ability to use this site.

When We May Disclose Your Personally Identifiable Information, Talentnow Communications Content, Data and Information

Talentnow may disclose your Personally Identifiable Information or the contents of your private communications if required to do so by law or court order. Your Personally Identifiable Information may also be disclosed if necessary in order to complete a transaction such as the fulfillment of an order or purchase placed by you.

Talentnow will in no way disclose the contents of your Talentnow communications other than to the intended recipient(s) unless required (1) by law or court order, (2) to protect Talentnow's rights and property, (3) to protect against unauthorized use of the Talentnow site, and (4) during emergencies such as when we believe someone's physical safety is at risk.

Also, certain technical processing of messages and their content may be required to: (1) send and receive messages; (2) conform to connecting networks' technical requirements; (3) conform to the limitations of the Service; or (4) conform to other similar requirements.

It is possible that as we continue to develop the Talentnow website and business, Talentnow and/or related assets may be acquired. In such a transaction, customer information may be transferred to the acquiring entity.

Security

This site has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and integrity of the information under our control. Although we make good faith efforts to store the information collected by the Talentnow service in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, we cannot guarantee complete security.

Other Websites or Links

This Website contains links to other websites. Talentnow is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

Opt-Out/Correct/Delete/Deactivate

You may elect not to receive future communications from Talentnow or to discontinue use of our service. If you are a registered user, please log in and visit your settings on the “Edit Profile” page of the website and uncheck the box related to sending information to you via email.

If you have previously made contact (by expressing interest in a job, or participating in communication, or referring someone else for a job) with Talentnow business partners, you must independently opt-out of communications from that individual company.

Individuals who wish to deactivate their Talentnow account may do so. Removed information may persist in backup or cached copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available to any user of Talentnow.

Talentnow allows its users the option to change information previously provided. This may be done through the following method:

* Log in to the Talentnow site, access your “Edit Profile” view. From here you can answer, delete, update or change any content that you have previously submitted.

Changes to this Policy

Talentnow reserves the right to modify this privacy policy at its sole discretion. Talentnow may notify registered users of any substantive changes in this policy. The policy at all times will be posted at the same location. Users are requested to go through the policy from time to time. Your continued use of the site after the changes are posted constitutes your agreement to the changes with regard to information collected in the past and in the future from you. If you do not agree to the changes, you may opt-out as described above.

Contacting the Web Site

We strive to do everything we can to protect the privacy of our users. Please feel free to share your feedback with us. Please write to [ privacy@talentnow.com](mailto:%20privacy@talentnow.com) If you have any questions about this privacy policy.
